

Veronica. Developer

+6287888302321 veyolie@gmail.com Tangerang, Indonesia

SUMMARY

I am very interested in developing an application or website. I love to learn more about developing an application or website. I want to search for more experience in the IT field because it's fun to study more about programming. I am very open to new knowledge in the IT field.

I want to learn more about developing an application or website. I want to search for more experience in the IT field because it's fun to study more about programming. I am very open to new knowledge in the IT field. Now I am focusing on learning in the field.

EXPERIENCE

06/2023 - Present

Software Engineer (Fintech)

PT. Finexus Group Jakarta

Work as a Backend developer as a software engineer for the end of the day (EOD) in a finance program. Help to maintain and build new programs.

- · Analyse programs that have to be enhanced
- Understanding of the business process and the flow of the program work in the scheduler or service
- Understand how to use Linux, query to search data, and analyze them.
- Tried to simplify the program and also make the program more efficient

06/2022 - 12/2022

Backend developer (Fintech)

PT. Finpoint Solusi Indonesia

Work as a backend developer as a restful API developer for website development and develop generating report program using Golang programing language.

- Develop a payment gateway and backend website program using Golang programming language and PostgreSQL as the Database.
- Understanding using docker and deploying program at the server.
- Understand how to use Elasticsearch to get transactions and generate a report.

01/2022 - 06/2022

Assistant Laboratory (Visual Programming)

Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Teaching Visual Programming in Universitas Multimedia Nusantara using Visual Studio.

- learned more about using the C# language
- I also learned about working together with my partner and building communication in class.
- Learning about how to transfer knowledge to the other student.

08/2021 - 12/2021

Assistant Laboratory (Probability Statistic)

Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Teaching Probability Statistics in University Multimedia Nusantara using R Studio.

- Learned how to work together with my partner
- learn more about R, have a good experience in teaching
- · have a good experience in teaching and communicate with the student

EDUCATION

2023 Information System

Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

Bachelor Degree

I am a system information student at Universitas Multimedia Nusantara with a GPA 3.72. Studying database oracle, building websites and applications, learning how to read flowcharts for

apps and businesses, and data visualization.

2019 Kristen Kanaan Tangerang

 SMA

CERTIFICATES

10/2020 - Present Gajiku First Place and Public Favorite at Startup Weekend

SKILLS

Linux	Intermediate	Docker	Intermediate
Golang	Intermediate	Figma	Basic
Java	Intermediate	SQL	Intermediate
HTML	Intermediate	phpmyadmin	Intermediate
C#	Intermediate	PostgreSQL	Intermediate
CSS	Basic	Oracle	Intermediate
PHP	Basic	Tableau	Basic

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Intermediate English Basic